Guide to the Max S. Baucus Papers 1958-2016 (bulk 1974-2014)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1958-2014; Series XIII; 29.6 linear feet; 281.9 gigabytes
  - Photographs, 1959-2013; Sub-series 1; 25.7 linear feet
    - 1981 0326 D.C. MM Blue Sky Cruise and Travel, March 26, 1981; Max Baucus with Blue Sky Cruise and Travel members Nancy Helgeth and Nina Hinderman of Whitefish, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/53)
    - 1981 0401 D.C. MM Lisa Fritzler and Ellis Murdock of Lodge Grass, April 1, 1981; Max Baucus with Lisa Fritzler and Ellis Murdock of Lodge Grass, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/54)
    - 1981 0402 D.C. MM Former Staff Steve Rovig and Family, April 2, 1981; Max Baucus in his office with staff member Steve Rovig and Rovig's family. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/55)
    - 1981 0402 D.C. MM Trina Rovig of Billings Eating Cookies, April 2, 1981; Max Baucus eating cookies in office with Trina Rovig of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/56)
    - 1981 0406 D.C. MM Lambert High School, April 6, 1981; Max Baucus on steps of the U.S. Capitol with Lambert High School senior class and chaperones. Chaperones: Jim and Doris Mullin, Marcia Williams. Students: Lisa Williams, Lori Mullin, Doug Strand, Pam Carda, Doug Whitney, Casey Mavity, Phil Fink, Todd Sheehan, Jake Lake, Tammy Vaira, Kyle Johnston, Nick Vaira, Beth Torgerson, and Dana Rosaaen. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/57)
    - 1981 0409-0418 F Middle East Trip with Senator Howard Baker and Others, April 9-18, 1981; Max Baucus on Middle East trip with Senator Howard Baker: At the Wailing Wall; with Moshe Dayan; with Prime Minister Menahem Begin; posed with group in front of ruins. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/58)
    - 1981 0429 D.C. MM Davis, Laughman, Donahue, Donahue, Davis, April 29, 1981; Max Baucus with Grace Davis and Dolores Laughnan of Havre, Montana; Daty Donahue of Washington, D.C.; Mary Donahue of St. Paul, Minnesota; and Bill Davis of Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/59)
    - 1981 04 F Spain King Juan Carlos and Others, April 1981; Max Baucus with Spanish King Juan Carlos and others. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/60)
    - 1981 04 MT Butte MHD Event, April 1981; Max Baucus speaking at a magnetohydrodynamics (MHD) event in Butte, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/61)
    - 1981 0501 D.C. MM Lynn Bishop and Christina Maek, May 1, 1981; Max Baucus with Lynn Bishop and Christina Mack of Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/62)
    - 1981 0511 D.C. MM Alexander Family of Hot Springs, May 11, 1981; Max Baucus with Susan, Brian, and Bridget Alexander of Hot Springs, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/63)
    - 1981 0513 D.C. MM Coolidge, Younger, Davis, Marbuss, May 13, 1981; Max Baucus with Christine Coolidge of Whitefish, Montana; Jenny Younger of Bozeman, Montana; Margaret Davis of Helena, Montana; and Jean Marbuss. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/64)
    - 1981 0516 D.C. MM Unknown Constituent, May 16, 1981; Max Baucus with a constituent. (Box-folder Series 13 - 9/65)
    - 1981 0521 D.C. MM Vietnam Veterans from Billings, May 21, 1981; Max Baucus with Vietnam veterans from Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/1)
    - 1981 05 D.C. MM Jacques Cousteau, May 1981; Max Baucus with Jacques Cousteau. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/2)
    - 1981 05 D.C. Reagan Economic Address Before Congress, May 1981; President Reagan giving an economic address in front of Congress, Vice President George Bush and Speaker Tip O'Neill visible. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/3)
    - 1981 05 Unknown Events with Constituents, May 1981; Max Baucus at unidentified events with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/4)
    - 1981 0604 D.C. MM Hollow Family of Helena, June 4, 1981; Max Baucus with John, Margaret, Lee Ann, and Peggy Hollow of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/5)
    - 1981 0610 D.C. MM Valley County Washington Focus, June 10, 1981; Max Baucus on steps of the U.S. Capitol with members of the Valley County Washington Focus Group. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/6)
    - 1981 0610 D.C. MM Washington Focus, June 10, 1981; Max Baucus on steps of the U.S. Capitol with members of the Washington Focus Group. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/7)
    - 1981 0611 D.C. MM Rose Skoog of Helena, June 11, 1981; Max Baucus with Rose Skoog of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/8)
    - 1981 0611 D.C. MM Tom Harris of Fishtail, June 11, 1981; Max Baucus with Tom Harris of Fishtail, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/9)
    - 1981 0617 MM MSB with Group of Younger Constituents on Capitol Steps, June 17, 1981; Max Baucus sitting on Capitol steps with group of young constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/10)
    - 1981 0618 D.C. MM Judy Collins, June 18, 1981; Max Baucus with Judy Collins. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/11)
    - 1981 0619 D.C. MM Unknown Constituent, June 19, 1981; Max Baucus with a constituent; running in a race. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/12)
    - 1981 0622 D.C. MM Maybe Page Clare M, June 22, 1981; Max Baucus with Clare (last name unknown), possibly a Senate Page. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/13)
    - 1981 0622 D.C. MM Page Tracy Outlaw, June 22, 1981; Max Baucus with Tracy Outlaw, a Senate Page. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/14)
    - 1981 0622 D.C. MM Periman, Klessins, Cavey, Cavey, June 22, 1981; Max Baucus with Scott and Mike Cavey of Missoula, Montana; Kathy Periman and Cindy Klessins of Deer Lodge, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/15)
    - 1981 0622 D.C. MM Young Family of Joliet, June 22, 1981; Max Baucus with Jim and Sandy Young and children David and Peter of Joliet, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/16)
    - 1981 0624 D.C. MM Ted and Claudia Brownlee of Lewistown, June 24, 1981; Max Baucus with Ted and Claudia Brownlee of Lewistown, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/17)
    - 1981 06 MT Helena Governors Cup, June 1981; Max Baucus running in the Helena Governor's Cup. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/18)
    - 1981 0910 D.C. Nike Capitol Challenge, September 10, 1981; Max Baucus running in the Nike Capitol Challenge with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/19-21)
    - 1981 0910 D.C. Sandra Day O'Connor and Strom Thurmond with Judiciary Committee Members, September 11, 1981; Max Baucus with Sandra Day O'Connor, Senator Strom Thurmond and members of the Senate Judiciary Committee. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/22)
    - 1981 0915 D.C. MM Glendenning, McCall, Dougherty, Young, September 15, 1981; Max Baucus with Thomas Glendenning of Miles City, Montana; Walt McCall of Great Falls, Montana; Al Dougherty of Helena, Montana; and Ken Young of Kalispell, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/23)
    - 1981 0917 D.C. MM Marjorie Crawford of Corvallis, September 17, 1981; Max Baucus with Marjorie Crawford of Corvallis, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/24)
    - 1981 0918 D.C. MM Former Staff Dick Hargesheimer and Family, September 18, 1981; Max Baucus with Dick Hargesheimer and family members Mary Lou Gibson and Jimmy Hocking. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/25)
    - 1981 0918 D.C. MM Mr. and Mrs. Aruthur Harker of Whitefish, September 18, 1981; Max Baucus with Mrs. and Mr. Arthur Harker of Whitefish, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/26)
    - 1981 0922 D.C. MM Ed Dawer of Clancy and Debbie Hall of Helena, September 22, 1981; Max Baucus with Ed Dawer of Clancy, Montana and Debbie Hall of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/27)
    - 1981 0924 D.C. MM Butte Senior Citizens, September 24, 1981; Max Baucus sitting on U.S. Capitol steps with senior citizens from Butte, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/28)
    - 1981 0929 D.C. MM March of Dimes Poster Child Richard Wagner, September 29, 1981; Max Baucus with March of Dimes poster child Richard Wagner. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/29)
    - 1981 1006 Unknown Speaking in Front of Seated Younger Constituents, October 6, 1981; Max Baucus speaking to a group of young constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/30)
    - 1981 1007 Unknown Ambassador Mike Mansfield, October 7, 1981; Max Baucus shaking hands with Ambassador Mike Mansfield. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/31)
    - 1981 1008 D.C. MM Glenn Roush of Cut Bank, October 8, 1981; Max Baucus with Glenn Roush of Cut Bank, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/32)
    - 1981 1028 D.C. Testifying at House Severance Hearing, October 28, 1981; Max Baucus testifying at a U.S. House of Representatives severance hearing. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/33)
    - 1981 10 D.C. MM MSB with Group of Seniors in Capitol Mansfield Room, October 1981; Max Baucus with constituents in the U.S. Capitol's Mike Mansfield Room. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/34)
    - 1981 1117 D.C. MM Energy Consumers and Producers Association, November 17, 1981; Max Baucus with Bud Stewart of the Energy Consumers and Producers Association of Oklahoma. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/35)
    - 1981 1119 D.C. MM Archbishop Raymond Hunthausen of Seattle, November 19, 1981; Max Baucus with Raymond G. Hunthausen, Archbishop of Seattle. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/36)
    - 1981 11 D.C. King Hussein of Jordan, November 1981; Max Baucus shaking hands with King Hussein of Jordan. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/37)
    - 1981 1202 D.C. MM Siderius Family of Kalispell and Warren McGee of Livingston, December 2, 1981; Max Baucus with Dolly, Linda, and Hank Siderius of Kalispell, Montana and Warren McGee of Livingston, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/38)
    - 1981 1207 Unknown Speaking at Occidental Life Forum, December 7, 1981; Max Baucus speaking at the Occidental Life Forum. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/39)
    - 1981 1209 D.C. MM Lynwood Hall of Georgia, December 9, 1981; Max Baucus with Lynwood Hall of Georgia. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/40)
    - 1981 1211 D.C. MM Former Staff Sheila Lopach, December 11, 1981; Max Baucus with former staffer Sheila Lopach. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/41)
    - 1981 D.C. All Staff Posed Outdoors, Max Baucus posed outdoors with staff. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/42)
    - 1981 D.C. Chief of Staff Robert (Steve) Browning and Unknown Constituent, Chief of Staff Robert (Steve) Browning and unidentified constituent. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/43)
    - 1981 D.C. MM Former Staff Intern Kim Brown of California, Max Baucus with former staff intern Kim Brown of California. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/44)
    - 1981 D.C. MM Former Staff Intern Mike Chapman, Max Baucus with former staff intern Mike Chapman. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/45)
    - 1981 D.C. MM Patty Jones of Gold Creek and Greg Plate of Ohio, Max Baucus with Patty Jones of Gold Creek, Montana and Greg Plate of Ohio. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/46)
    - 1981 D.C. MM Peter Fenn of D.C., Max Baucus shaking hands with Peter Fenn of Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/47)
    - 1981 D.C. National Youth Science Camp, Max Baucus with two members of the National Youth Science Camp. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/48)
    - 1981 D.C. Unknown Event, Meeting with Constituents and Staff in Office, Max Baucus meeting with constituents; with staff in office. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/49)
    - 1981 D.C. Unknown Party Maybe Staff Birthday, Max Baucus with staff at a party. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/50)
    - 1981 MT Helena Staff Meeting, Max Baucus and staff at a staff meeting in Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/51)
    - 1981 Running with Diana Riley and Tom Judge, Max Baucus at a running event with Dianna Riley and Montana Governor Tom Judge. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/52)
    - 1982 0105 Unknown Speaking at International Consumer Credit Conference, January 5, 1982; Max Baucus speaking at the International Consumer Credit Conference. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/53)
    - 1982 0119 D.C. MM MT Wheat Commission, January 19, 1982; Max Baucus with members and officials of the Montana Wheat Commission: George Skarda of Denton, Montana; Assistant Administrator Jim Christianson of Great Falls, Montana; Dana and Shirley Fitzgerald of Power, Montana; Rick and Mary Sampsen of Dagmar, Montana; Jim and Diane Jenks of Hogeland, Montana; Glenn Moore of Baker, Montana; Bill Brinkel of Broadview, Montana; Chairman Ed Keil of Conrad, Montana and his wife. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/54)
    - 1982 0125 D.C MM MT Wheatgrowers, January 25, 1982; Max Baucus with members of the Montana Wheatgrowers Association and interns Andrea Wollard and Tom Pellegrene. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/55)
    - 1982 0126 D.C. National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, January 26, 1982; Max Baucus with members of the National Council of Farmer Cooperatives: Ron Bokma, Director of Farm Credit Administration, of Conrad, Montana; Gordon Matheson, Chairman of the Board of Directors of the Grain Terminal Association, of Conrad, Montana; Arnold Peterson, Director of Grain Terminal Association, of Havre, Montana; Gerald Redlin, Director of Grain Terminal Association - Route 1, Gof Lambert, Montana; Sigurd (last name unknown), Director of Farmers Union Marketing and Processing Association - Route 1, of Havre, Montana; Ed Melby, Director of Cenex, of Billings, Montana; Lloyd Kaercher, Director of Cenex, of Havre, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/56)
    - 1982 0126 D.C. Reagan State of the Union Address, January 26, 1982; President Ronald Reagan delivering the State of the Union Address, Vice President George Bush and Speaker Tip O'Neill visible in background. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/57)
    - 1982 0128 D.C. MM Lark and Jean Carter of Bozeman, January 28, 1982; Max Baucus with Lark and Jean Carter of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/58)
    - 1982 0128 D.C. MM Roberta Thennis of Helena, January 28, 1982; Max Baucus with Roberta Thennis of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/59)
    - 1982 0129 D.C. MM Daphne Meimaridis of Ohio, January 29, 1982; Max Baucus with Daphne Meimaridis of Oberlin, Ohio. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/60)
    - 1982 0129 D.C. MM Greg Ingraham of Ronan, January 29, 1982; Max Baucus with Greg Ingraham of Ronan, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/61)
    - 1982 0129 D.C. MM MT Mining Association, January 29, 1982; Max Baucus with Gary Langley, Executive director of the Montana Mining Association, of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/62)
    - 1982 0202 D.C. MM Billings Housing Authority, February 2, 1982; Max Baucus with members of Billings Housing Authority Pete Langdorf and Angie Cormier of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/63)
    - 1982 0202 D.C. MM MT Hospital Association, February 2, 1982; Max Baucus with members of the Montana Hospital Association (MHA) Team of the Montana Congressional Visitation Delegation: Chairman of the Board Tom Gillespie of Polson, Montana; former Chairman Sister Michel Pantenburg of Billings, Montana; former Chairman George Clark of Kalispell, Montana; Dean Jellison, Chairman of the National Council of Hospital Governing Boards, of Kalispell, Montana; MHA President William Leary of Helena, Montana; MHA Senior Vice President Ken Rutledge of Helena, Montana; Controller/Associate Administrator Gene Johnson of Kalispell, Montana; Executive Secretary Marge Leary of Helena, Montana; Home Health Coordinator Chris Gillespie of Polson, Montana; Chairman of the Board of Trustees Gus Korb of Havre, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/64)
    - 1982 0203 D.C. MM Public Power Association, February 3, 1982; Max Baucus with Wilbur Anderson of Dillon, Montana and Norman Jacox, General Manager of the Northwest Public Power Association, of Vancouver, Washington. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/65)
    - 1982 0204 D.C. Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak, February 4, 1982; Max Baucus shaking hands with Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/66)
    - 1982 0204 D.C. MM Jack and Norine Pellegrini of Anaconda, February 4, 1982; Max Baucus with Jack and Norine Pellegrini of Anaconda, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/67)
    - 1982 0204 D.C. MM Jack Nichels of Fort Peck, February 4, 1982; Max Baucus with Jack Nichels of Fort Peck, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/68)
    - 1982 0204 D.C. MM Jim Lumsen of Great Falls, February 4, 1982; Max Baucus with Jim Lumsen of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/69)
    - 1982 0204 D.C. MM Jim Walorath of Bridger, February 4, 1982; Max Baucus with Jim Walorath of Bridger, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/70)
    - 1982 0204 D.C. MM Patty Harper of Helena, February 4, 1982; Max Baucus with Patty Harper of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/71)
    - 1982 0205 D.C. MM Jim Flanagan of Helena, February 5, 1982; Max Baucus with Jim Flanagan of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/72)
    - 1982 0209 D.C. MM Credit Unions Stakeholders, February 9, 1982; Max Baucus with credit union stakeholders Gene Rice, Manager of State Capitol Employees Credit Union, of Helena, Montana; Jeff Kirkland, Director of Government Gelations for the Montana Credit Unions League, of Helena, Montana; Herb Walberg, President of the Montana Credit Unions League, of Helena, Montana; Clinton VanAtta of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 10/73)
    - 1982 0209 D.C. MM Zack Russell of Glendive, February 9, 1982; Max Baucus with Zack Russell of Glendive, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/1)
    - 1982 0210 D.C. MM Farm Women's Forum, February 10, 1982; Max Baucus with members of the Farm Women's Forum Ester Rudd of Malta, Montana; Yvonne Snider of Lewistown, Montana; and Nancy Espy of Boyes, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/2)
    - 1982 0210 D.C. MM Max Barker of Augusta, February 10, 1982; Max Baucus with Max Barker of Augusta, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/3)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM American Bankers Association, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus with representatives to the American Bankers Association Leadership Conference. Left to right: John Cadby, Executive Vice President of the Montana Bankers Association; Donald Olsson, Sr., President of the Ronan State Bank; Lynn Grobel, President of the First National Bank in Glasgow, Montana; and Erle Gross, President of the Little Horn State Bank in Hardin, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/4)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM Certificate of Appreciation from National Citizens Crime Prevention Campaign, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus presenting a certificate of appreciation from the National Citizens' Crime Prevention Campaign to Ruth Dahl, Executive Director of the Community Crime Prevention Council, of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/5)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM Jimmy Hynson of Senate Service Department, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus with Jimmy Hynson, from the U.S. Senate Service Department. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/6)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM Mike Bowman and Bob Lukes of Missoula, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus with Mike Bowman and Bob Lukes of Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/7)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM Ruth Dahl of Billings Crimestoppers, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus presenting a certificate of appreciation from the National Citizens' Crime Prevention Campaign to Ruth Dahl, Executive Director of the Community Crime Prevention Council, of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/8)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM Thomas and Anna Nichols of Wolf Point, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus with Thomas and Anna Nichols of Wolf Point, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/9)
    - 1982 0211 D.C. MM Unknown Constituents, February 11, 1982; Max Baucus with constituents. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/10)
    - 1982 0223 D.C. MM Barbara and Allan Evans of Missoula, Mike Stephens of Helena, February 23, 1982; Max Baucus with Barbara and Allan Evans of Missoula, Montana, and Mike Stephens, Executive Director of the Montana Association of Counties, of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/11)
    - 1982 0225 D.C. MM Lowell and Susan Bartels of Helena, February 25, 1982; Max Baucus with Lowell and Susan Bartels of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/12)
    - 1982 0225 D.C. MM Mike Penfold BLM Director of Billings, February 25, 1982; Max Baucus with Bureau of Land Management (BLM) Director Mike Penfold of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/13)
    - 1982 0225 D.C. MM Scott, Deming Humphry, DeLeo of Great Falls, February 25, 1982; Max Baucus with Suzie Scott, Lisa Deming, Dan Humphrey, and Lisa DeLeo of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/14)
    - 1982 0301 D.C. MM Garry Wunderwald of Helena Department of Highways, March 1, 1982; Max Baucus with Garry Wunderwald, from the Helena Department of Highways, of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/15)
    - 1982 0302 D.C. MM George Erickson of Great Falls, March 2, 1982; Max Baucus with George Erickson of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/16)
    - 1982 0302 D.C. MM Margaret Warden of Great Falls, March 2, 1982; Max Baucus with Margaret Warden, member of the National Library Commission, of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/17)
    - 1982 0302 D.C. MM Maureen Bureson of Great Falls, March 2, 1982; Max Baucus with Maureen Bureson of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/18)
    - 1982 0302 D.C. MM Public Service Commission, March 2, 1982; Max Baucus with Tom Schneider, Public Service Commission Chairman, of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/19)
    - 1982 0302 D.C. MM Yoshi Ogawa of D.C., March 2, 1982; Max Baucus with Yoshi Ogawa of Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/20)
    - 1982 0303 D.C. MM Ed Melby of Billings, Lloyd and Audrey Kaercher of Havre, March 3, 1982; Max Baucus with Ed Melby of Billings, Montana and Lloyd and Audrey Kaercher of Havre, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/21)
    - 1982 0316 D.C. MM Mont Cassidy of Boilmakers of Seeley Lake, March 16, 1982; Max Baucus shaking hands with Mont S. Cassidy of the Seeley Lake Boilermakers. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/22)
    - 1982 0318 D.C. MM Armesher, Keller, Thompson, Ruff, Pilcher, Haines, McDonald, March 18, 1982; Max Baucus with Charlean Keller, Bill and Jean Thompson, Don and Dianne Ruff of Billings, Montana; Ray Armesher, Margaret Pilcher, Tom Haines, and Marie McDonald of Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/23)
    - 1982 0319 D.C. MM Doinell, Janet and Allison Ball of Polson, March 19, 1982; Max Baucus with Mr. and Mrs. Doinell and Janet and Allison Ball of Polson, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/24)
    - 1982 0323 D.C. MM Cystic Fibrosis Foundation Poster Children Kimberly, Kristie, and Brett Pearce, March 23, 1982; Max Baucus with Kimberly, Kristie, and Brett Pearce, poster children for the Cystic Fibrosis Foundation. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/25)
    - 1982 0323 D.C. MM Dave Sexton, Helen Witts, Bill Bradford, John Board, March 23, 1982; Max Baucus with Dave Sexton and John Board of Helena, Montana; Helen Witts of Kalispell, Montana; Bill Bradford of Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/26)
    - 1982 0323 D.C. MM Leuthold, Grosen, Johnson, Mattson, Martin, March 23, 1982; Max Baucus with Bud Leuthold of Billings, Montana; Knud Grosen of Big Sandy, Montana; Randy Johnson of Haugan, Montana; David Mattson of Chester, Montana; Troy Martin of Winifred, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/27)
    - 1982 0324 D.C. MM Former Staff Intern Web Brown, March 24, 1982; Max Baucus with former staff intern Web Scott Brown of California. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/28)
    - 1982 0324 D.C. MM Meyer, Beck, Wheeler, Haderlui, March 24, 1982; Max Baucus with Steve Meyer, Ray Beck, Terry Wheeler of Helena, Montana; Van Haderlui of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/29)
    - 1982 0326 D.C. MM Irv Dellinger of Helena, Wally Steffan of Billings, March 26, 1982; Max Baucus with Irv Dellinger of Helena and Wally Steffan of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/30)
    - 1982 0330 D.C. MM Commissioner of Higher Education, March 30, 1982; Max Baucus with Irving Dayton, Commissioner of Higher Education, of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 11/31)